ewealth.com 2001-04-29

# ewealth.com

**ewealth Privacy Policy

**ewealth's Commitment to Privacy:**

Your information will not be sold to anyone. **ewealth** does not collect personal information without your specifically and knowingly providing it, therefore we do not store permanent "cookies" on your computer. Other financial Web sites may implement "cookies" to track user profiles and store sensitive information, but ewealth does not place any user information on your computer, instead stores personal information on protected servers. 

**ewealth** will only share personal information under limited circumstances outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

When we will release your information: 

    1. If the law requires us to release your information, such as under search warrant, valid demand, or other legally valid inquiry or order, **ewealth** will disclose information to the proper authorities. **ewealth** may also disclose information to serve an apparent public interest, in good faith, to protect against criminal activity such as fraud and money laundering. Furthermore, we may disclose information to outside parties to protect the interests of **ewealth** Holdings, Inc., such as returning insufficiently funded checks.
    2. If we have your advanced consent, **ewealth** will disclose only the information required to identify you to other parties, i.e. your credit history with **ewealth** for the credit approval process with an outside vendor. We may use your personal information to advise you about our products and services, along with those of our outside vendors. **ewealth** maintains strict privacy policies with outside vendors, and limits the distribution of your information to only what is necessary to conduct business with you. 
    3. We provide only the necessary amount of information to our service vendors, who may provide goods and services such as printed checks and credit cards.

**ewealth** employees with access to your confidential agreement may not disclose your information (excluding use for business purposes) and are required to safeguard this information. Your account information is limited to individuals in the company who offer you our products and services. All employees have signed agreements with ewealth to ensure the protection of your privacy. 

Your privacy and confidentiality are of utmost importance to **ewealth**. As a member of the NASD, SIPC, and MSRB, **ewealth** is required to obtain personal information about you in order to service your account(s). Due to regulatory policies, **ewealth** must obtain personal identity information such as social security/Tax ID numbers, home addresses and telephone numbers, etc. Please be aware that ewealth does not share this information and will only release it under the limited circumstances outlined above. 

**ewealth** regularly communicates with its clients through all types of channels, including phone, fax, mail and email. Users may receive stock order confirmations, margin calls, account statements, or various other information that ewealth must send to its clients. 

We fully understand your concern regarding our use of your information, and have created this privacy policy to ensure your safety on the Internet. 

**We Protect Your Account Integrity**

 **ewealth** takes every technological precaution to ensure the security of your account. All Internet transactions with ewealth require a secure connection. We protect your account information by placing it on the secure portion of our Web site. ewealth uses VeriSign Secure Server Digital IDSM, Apache Secure Server and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your communications through server authentication and data encryption. We recommend that all customers use a 128-bit SSL-capable browser to access our sites. Browsers such as Netscape 4.06 and Microsoft Internet Explorer 4.01 will automatically enable SSL upon logging into your ewealth account. ewealth also uses firewalls as security checkpoints to ensure accurate data entry from the Internet into our internal systems. By providing encryption between the client and internal systems, data is filtered and protected from unauthorized access and modification. You must enter a unique User Name and Password each time you access your account information. You may also use the Log Off button located throughout the ewealth website to exit your account without closing your browser. Our network and databases are fully redundant and periodically backed up to preserve account integrity. 

**Accuracy of Personal Information**

We continuously evaluate our efforts, as well as emerging technologies that may better protect your privacy. If you identify errors in your personal information, it is imperative that you contact **ewealth** to ensure accurate personal information. Keeping us informed of changes such as address and phone number changes also allows us to make necessary corrections and offer effective and accurate products and services to you. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at 

**
